# JENNIE L. MOUSSA

155 W. 9th Street ■ Bayonne, NJ 07002 ■ ② (717) 303-6596 ■ ☑ jennie.moussa118@gmail.com

Energetic, versatile, and results-driven individual with excellent qualifications and experience to support projects and activities requiring strong communication, analytical, problem solving, and technical skills. Works effectively, independently, and collaboratively as part of a team in demanding environments. Uses well-developed interpersonal skills to establish positive working relationships with customers, co-workers, and all levels of company management.

## SKILLS AND CAPABILITIES

- Data Compilation and Analysis
- Extracting / Manipulating Data
- Analyzing / Resolving Problems
- Quantitative and Analytical Skills
- Financial Services / Investments
- Ad-Hoc Reporting and Analysis
- Operations/Process Improvement
- Meticulous Attention To Details
- Business/Technology/Marketing
- Applications / Software / Systems
- Clear / Effective Communication
- Marketing Analytics and Metrics

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Sales Associate, BNY Mellon, New York, NY

2017 - Present

Leverage exceptional analytical, creative, organizational, and communication skills to provide a high level of sales and marketing support to the sales officers. Held directly accountable for developing sales presentations, tracking new/pending business leads, identifying opportunities to enhance client relationships and retention, and planning, coordinating, and participating in various industry seminars, firm presentations, and other entertainment events.

• Complete duties with minimal supervision/direction, handle time sensitive information appropriately, establish priorities and manage daily workflow, and ensure the timely completion of projects, tasks, and responsibilities.

## Corporate Actions Associate II, Fidelity Investments, Jersey City, NJ

2015 - 2017

Held accountable for demonstrating initiative, communication and problem solving skills, and excellent financial services industry knowledge to support a wide range of analytical and relationship building activities. Directly responsible for developing and maintaining relationships with vendors and engaging cross-functional resources including operations, pricing, and legal to effectively manage new and existing client and vendor relationships.

- Provided analysis disclosing risk in dividends processing, reviewed dividend announcements for payments and elections, ensured accurate and timely distributions, and quickly resolved any outstanding or incomplete items.
- Recognized for performance and results including nominee/participant in TAP (Talent Acceleration Program) and two promotions. Assisted management and team with problem solving and training/supporting new hires.

#### Marketing Analyst, Consultants 2 Go, Newark, NJ

2014 - 2015

Fully responsible for applying strong analytical, communication, problem solving, and leadership abilities while performing market research, analysis, and reporting to assess overall impact of business opportunities. Accountable for developing research projects for specific business issues and analyzing sales activities, marketing campaigns, organizations, customers, pricing, and competitors through the use of various charts, graphs, and explanatory texts.

- Displayed excellent capacity to meet deadlines, build rapport with individuals at all levels and backgrounds, and to support business goals by facilitating an environment that consistently achieved or exceeded expectations.
- Integrated market research information into CRM to assist in lead development, drafted/published press releases and job announcements, and maintained relations through proactive contact with employees and consultants.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in Marketing and Finance, New Jersey Institute of Technology, Newark, NJ (GPA: 3.6)

**Computer:** Microsoft Office (Word/Excel/PowerPoint/Access/Outlook), MS Project, MS Visio, Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop, Bloomberg, Salesforce, Databases, Constant Contact, Citibank/Securities Platform, ShadoSuite